http://www.speedtechinternational.com/privacy-policy/

Welcome to our Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us.
Speedtech International, Inc is located at:
Mailing: PO Box 246. Factory: 1405 16th Street.
Racine, WI 53401.  United States.
Phone: 262-635-9393
It is Speedtech‘s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to www.speedtechinternational.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “www.speedtechinternational.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
– Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Speedtech collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Speedtech International, Inc’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Speedtech’s website visitors use its website.  Speedtech collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://www.speedtechinternational.com blog posts. Speedtech only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
– Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Speedtech’s websites choose to interact with Speedtech in ways that require Speedtech to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Speedtech gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://www.speedtechinternational.com to provide a username and email address.
– Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
– Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
– speedtechinternational.com uses Google AdWords for remarketing
Www.speedtechinternational.com uses the remarketing services to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
– Aggregated Statistics
Speedtech may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Speedtech may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Speedtech does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
– Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Speedtech uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Speedtechuses cookies to help Speedtech identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.speedtechinternational.com, and their website access preferences. Speedtechvisitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Speedtech International, Inc’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Speedtech International, Inc’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Speedtech International, Inc’s use of cookies.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Speedtech may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Speedtech International, Inc’s sole discretion. Speedtech encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Search
Product by categoryBerry Compliant
Cable Ties
Cinch Straps
Tapes
Custom Printing
Mounting/Hanging
Specialty Fasteners
Fire Retardant
SPEEDWRAP® Brand
VELCRO® Brand
SPEEDWRAP® Product Line Brochure
Thank you for Signing Up
Join Our Newsletter
We do NOT share your emails. We only send our news stories, application advice and special offers. You may unsubscribe at anytime. Thank you!
Please correct the marked field(s) below.
First Name
*
1,true,1,First Name,2
Last Name *
1,true,1,Last Name,2
Company Name
1,false,1,Company Name,2
Email *
1,true,6,Contact Email,2
Customer Type *
Do-It-YourselferProfessional Contractor/Installer/MaintenanceDistributorDesigner/SpecifierA/V or RentalManufacturerOther
1,true,3,Customer Type,2
Industry *
DataComOEM / ManufacturingMaintenance, Repair, OperationsAudio VideoAutomotive /TransportationMedicalConstructionSafetyElectricalIndustrial AutomationOutdoor / RecreationMusicMarineMilitary/ GovernmentRCRoboticsOther
1,true,3,Industry,2
Lead Source
ShopifyEmailOnline ShopTradeshow-BICSI2019ChatTradeshowOtherChat – Online StoreCorporate WebsiteChat – Corporate WebsiteFacebookTwitterExisting Speedtech DistributorPhoneImportGoogleplusBICSI-2020NetworkingContact UsCold callSocial MediaWeb FormsTrade ShowsWebinarsOrganic SearchReferralsChatAdvertisements
1,false,3,Lead Source,2
*Required Fields
About Us
Shop
Blog
Distributors
Custom Printing
Wholesale
MAILING ADDRESS:
Speedtech International Inc.
P.O. Box 246
Racine, WI 53401, USA
SHIPPING / RECEIVING: Speedtech International Inc.2410 Norwood CtRacine, WI 53403, USA
SALES PHONE:
Domestic (800) 771-3896
International
(01) 262-635-9393
SALES FAX NUMBER:
